https://pancreatica.org/privacy-policy/

Cancer Patients Alliance is a 501(c)(3) non-profit. Initiatives include Pancreatica.org, ToFightCancer.com, PancreaticCancerAlliance.org, and CancerPatientsAlliance.org.
All DONATIONS are tax-deductible.
Facebook-f
Twitter
Envelope
Instagram
Pancreatic cancer patients and families still need you.
Make an impact today, that lasts a lifetime.
DONATE TODAY
Home
PANCREATIC CANCER TOPICS
Pancreatic Cancer: Assorted Topics
Alternative, Complementary and Holistic Treatment
Classic Pancreatic Cancer FAQ
Neuroendocrine tumors, Islet-cell and Carcinoid tumors
Pancreatic Cancer Causes and Risk Factors
Pancreatic Cancer Symptoms and Signs
What is Pancreatic Cancer?
BLOG
About
Mission Statement
Why the Name Pancreatica
Science Board
STORIES
Brian Pochel
Dale Haskell
Pancreatic Cancer Symptoms and Signs
What is Pancreatic Cancer?
BLOG
About
Mission Statement
Why the Name Pancreatica
Science Board
STORIES
Brian Pochel
Dale Haskell
Next
You have likely found us either because you have pancreatic cancer, or care about someone who does.
Our mission is to promote awareness, increase education, and further pancreatic cancer research aimed at early diagnosis.
Click Here to Contact usPancreatic cancer is the 3rd leading cause of cancer-related death in the U.S. It is expected to become the 2nd leading cause of cancer-related death by the year 2020. We need to find the disease earlier!Donate to Research
Our aim is to present impartial knowledge about pancreatic cancer whereby interested parties can access the range of existing treatment options, to aid patient/doctor partnerships, and thus help medical teams optimize personal treatment strategies.Click Here to Support the CausePancreatic cancer is the most aggressive of the major cancers, and the least funded. It is nearly always diagnosed too late with 80% of pancreatic cancer patients having a terminal disease.
Click Here to make a tax-deductible DonationTogether we can make a difference! Recently, a seasoned specialist told us that we had the highest social good to donation ratio that they had ever seen in any non-profit. We put all donations to serious use.
Click Here to find ways to Help or Donate Pancreatic cancer is very aggressive. Fortunately together, so are we. There are many ways in which you can help the fight and make an impact for pancreatic cancer. Find the best way for you by clicking the link below. Click Here to find ways to Help or Donate
Previous
Next
Owner and Data Controller
Cancer Patients Alliance owns and operates https://pancreatica.org/ website.
This Website collects some Personal Data from its Users.
Owner’s contact email: info@pancreatica.org.
Owner’s address: 312 Fountain Avenue, Pacific Grove, CA 93950, USA.
Definitions and Legal References
Personal Data (or Data)
Any information that directly, indirectly, or in connection with other information – including a personal identification number – allows for the identification or identifiability of a natural person.
Usage Data
Information collected automatically through this Website (or third-party services employed in this Website), which can include: the IP addresses or domain names of the computers utilized by the Users who use this Website, the URI addresses (Uniform Resource Identifier), the time of the request, the method utilized to submit the request to the server, the size of the file received in response, the numerical code indicating the status of the server’s answer (successful outcome, error, etc.), the country of origin, the features of the browser and the operating system utilized by the User, the various time details per visit (e.g., the time spent on each page within the Website) and the details about the path followed within the Website with special reference to the sequence of pages visited, and other parameters about the device operating system and/or the User’s IT environment.
User
The individual using this Website who, unless otherwise specified, coincides with the Data Subject.
Data Subject
The natural person to whom the Personal Data refers.
Data Processor (or Data Supervisor)
The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes Personal Data on behalf of the Controller, as described in this privacy policy.
Data Controller (or Owner)
The natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of Personal Data, including the security measures concerning the operation and use of this website. The Data Controller, unless otherwise specified, is the Owner of this website.
This Website
The means by which the Personal Data of the User is collected and processed.
Service
The service provided by this website as described in the relative terms (if available) and on this site/website.
European Union (or EU)
Unless otherwise specified, all references made within this document to the European Union include all current member states to the European Union and the European Economic Area.
Cookies
Small sets of data stored in the User’s device.
Legal Information
This privacy statement has been prepared based on provisions of multiple legislations, including Art. 13/14 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation). This privacy policy relates solely to this website, if not stated otherwise within this document.
Types of Data Collected
Among the types of Personal Data that this website collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Cookies, Usage Data, First Name, Last Name, Physical Address, Email Address, Phone Number, Credit Card Number, Expiration, CVC and Billing Zip Code.
Complete details on each type of Personal Data collected are provided in the dedicated sections of this privacy policy or by specific explanation texts displayed prior to the Data collection. Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or, in case of Usage Data, collected automatically when using this website.
Unless specified otherwise, all Data requested by this website is mandatory and failure to provide this Data may make it impossible for this website to provide its services. In cases where this website specifically states that some Data is not mandatory, Users are free not to communicate this Data without consequences to the availability or the functioning of the Service.
Users who are uncertain about which Personal Data is mandatory are welcome to contact the Owner.
Any use of Cookies – or of other tracking tools – by this website or by the owners of third-party services used by this website serves the purpose of providing the Service required by the User, in addition to any other purposes described in the present document and in its Cookie Policy, if available.
Users are responsible for any third-party Personal Data obtained, published or shared through this website and confirm that they have the third party’s consent to provide the Data to the Owner.
Mode and Place of Processing the Data
Methods of Processing
The Owner takes appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data.
The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Owner, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of this website (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third-party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Owner at any time.
Legal Basis of Processing
The Owner may process Personal Data relating to Users if one of the following applies:
Users have given their consent for one or more specific purposes. Note: Under some legislations the Owner may be allowed to process Personal Data until the User objects to such processing (“opt-out”), without having to rely on consent or any other of the following legal bases. This, however, does not apply, whenever the processing of Personal Data is subject to European data protection law;
provision of Data is necessary for the performance of an agreement with the User and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof;
processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which the Owner is subject;
processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the Owner;
processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner or by a third party.
In any case, the Owner will gladly help to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Data is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.
Place
The Data is processed at the Owner’s operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located.
Depending on the User’s location, data transfers may involve transferring the User’s Data to a country other than their own. To find out more about the place of processing of such transferred Data, Users can check the section containing details about the processing of Personal Data.
Users are also entitled to learn about the legal basis of Data transfers to a country outside the European Union or to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more countries, such as the UN, and about the security measures taken by the Owner to safeguard their Data.
If any such transfer takes place, Users can find out more by checking the relevant sections of this document or inquire with the Owner using the information provided in the contact section.
Retention Time
Personal Data shall be processed and stored for as long as required by the purpose they have been collected for. Therefore:
Personal Data collected for purposes related to the performance of a contract between the Owner and the User shall be retained until such contract has been fully performed.
Personal Data collected for the purposes of the Owner’s legitimate interests shall be retained as long as needed to fulfill such purposes. Users may find specific information regarding the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner within the relevant sections of this document or by contacting the Owner.
The Owner may be allowed to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever the User has given consent to such processing, as long as such consent is not withdrawn. Furthermore, the Owner may be obliged to retain Personal Data for a longer period whenever required to do so for the performance of a legal obligation or upon order of an authority.
Once the retention period expires, Personal Data shall be deleted. Therefore, the right to access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after expiration of the retention period.
The Purposes of Processing
The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Owner to provide its Services, as well as for the following potential purposes: analytics, interaction with external social networks and platforms, user database management, remarketing and behavioral targeting, interaction with live chat platforms, displaying content from external platforms, and platform services and hosting.
Users can find further detailed information about such purposes of processing and about the specific Personal Data used for each purpose in the respective sections of this document.
Cookie Policy
Types of Cookies or Third Parties That Install Cookies
Some of the services listed below collect statistics in an anonymized and aggregated form and may not require the consent of the User or may be managed directly by the Owner – depending on how they are described – without the help of third parties.
If any third party operated services are listed among the tools below, these may be used to track Users’ browsing habits – in addition to the information specified herein and without the Owner’s knowledge. Please refer to the privacy policy of the listed services for detailed information.
How to Provide or Withdraw Consent to the Installation of Cookies
In addition to what is specified in this document, the User can manage preferences for Cookies directly from within their own browser and prevent – for example – third parties from installing Cookies. Through browser preferences, it is also possible to delete Cookies installed in the past, including the Cookies that may have saved the initial consent for the installation of Cookies by this website. Users can, for example, find information about how to manage Cookies in the most commonly used browsers at the following addresses: Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Apple Safari and Microsoft Internet Explorer.
With regard to Cookies installed by third parties, Users can manage their preferences and withdrawal of their consent by clicking the related opt-out link (if provided), by using the means provided in the third party’s privacy policy, or by contacting the third party.
Notwithstanding the above, the Owner informs that Users may follow the instructions provided on the subsequently linked initiatives by the EDAA (EU), the Network Advertising Initiative (US) and the Digital Advertising Alliance (US), DAAC (Canada), DDAI (Japan) or other similar services. Such initiatives allow Users to select their tracking preferences for most of the advertising tools. The Owner thus recommends that Users make use of these resources in addition to the information provided in this document.
Since the installation of third-party Cookies and other tracking systems through the services used within this Website cannot be technically controlled by the Owner, any specific references to Cookies and tracking systems installed by third parties are to be considered indicative. In order to obtain complete information, the User is kindly requested to consult the privacy policy for the respective third-party services listed in this document.
Given the objective complexity surrounding the identification of technologies based on Cookies, Users are encouraged to contact the Owner should they wish to receive any further information on the use of Cookies by this Website.
Detailed Information on the Processing of Personal Data
Personal Data may be collected for the following purposes and may use the following services:
Analytics
The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.
Google Analytics (Google, Inc.)
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services (if installed). Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy | Opt Out.
Google Ads (Google AdWords) Conversion Tracking (Google, Inc.)
Google Ads is a powerful conversion tracking tool that allows to identify how well the ad campaign is generating leads, sales, downloads, email sign-ups, and other key actions on the website (if installed).
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Interaction with External Social Networks and Platforms
This type of service allows interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of this Website. The interaction and information obtained through this Website are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network. This type of service might still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.
Facebook Like Button and Social Widgets (Facebook, Inc.)
The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook, Inc. (if installed).
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Twitter Share Button and Social Widgets (Twitter, Inc.)
The Tweet and Follow buttons are social buttons that allow website visitors to easily share the content with the followers on Twitter and enable them to easily engage with followers Twitter accounts (if installed).
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Google Plus Button and Social Widgets (Google, Inc.)
The LinkedIn button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the LinkedIn social network provided by LinkedIn Corporation (if installed).
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
FeedBurner (Google, Inc.)
FeedBurner is a web feed management provider that offers custom RSS feeds and management tools to bloggers, podcasters, and other web-based content publishers (if installed).
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Platform Services and Hosting
These services have the purpose of hosting and running key components of this Website, therefore allowing the provision of this Website from within a unified platform. Such platforms provide a wide range of tools to the Owner – e.g. analytics, user registration, commenting, database management, e-commerce, payment processing – that imply the collection and handling of Personal Data. Some of these services work through geographically distributed servers, making it difficult to determine the actual location where the Personal Data are stored.
Register.com (Web.com Group, Inc.)
Register.com is a technology company which specializes in domain name registration, web hosting and online marketing, and this Website’s domain name registrar.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
1&1 Internet Web Hosting (1&1 Internet Inc.)
1&1 Internet is a web hosting company that provides shared hosting, cloud hosting and dedicated servers and hosts this Website.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
WordPress.com (Automattic Inc.)
WordPress.com is a platform provided by Automattic Inc. that allows the Owner to build, run and host this Website.
Personal Data collected: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
WordPress Plugins
WordPress plugins are pieces of software containing a group of functions that can be added to a WordPress website in order to extend functionality or add new features. The Owner encourages the Users to familiarize themselves with Privacy Policies of the most commonly used WordPress plugins regardless if they are actually used on this Website or not.
AdWords Conversion Tracking Code (Kansas City SEO)
AdWords Conversion Tracking Code plugin adds AdWords remarketing code in order to display the ads on your site (if installed).
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Contact Developer for Usage Details.
BackWPup (Inpsyde)
BackWPup plugin (if installed) can be used to save your complete installation including /wp-content/ and push them to an external Backup Service, like Dropbox, S3, FTP and many more. With a single backup .zip file you are able to easily restore an installation.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: Germany – Privacy Policy.
Call To Action Box (Think Industries, LLC)
Call To Action Box plugin (if installed) offers an easy way to add call to action to your WordPress site.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Calls to Action (InboundWP, LLC)
Calls to Action plugin (if installed) creates calls to action for your WordPress site, which allows the ability to monitor and track conversion rates, and run a/b or multivariate split tests on calls to action.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Contact Developer for Usage Details.
Clear Cache For Me (WebHead)
Clear Cache For Me plugin (if installed) purges all cache on WPEngine, W3 Total Cache, WP Super Cache, WP Fastest Cache when updating widgets, menus, settings, and forces a browser to reload a theme’s CSS and JS files.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Contact Developer for Usage Details.
Continuous Announcement Scroller (gopiplus.com)
Continuous Announcement Scroller plugin (if installed) creates an announcement widget that allows the message to scroll vertically from bottom to top like roller displaying many messages at the same time.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Contact Developer for Usage Details.
Donately Integration (Fifty & Fifty)
Donately Integration plugin (if installed) allows non-profit groups to take secure donations from the widget in a sidebar or using the shortcode on any page on the website.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Contact Developer for Usage Details.
Export All URLs (Atlas Gondal)
Export All URLs plugin (if installed) allows to check how many pages and posts (including custom post types) are published, drafted or future-scheduled on the website.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: Pakistan – Contact Developer for Usage Details.
Google Analytics for WordPress (MonsterInsights, LLC)
This Google Analytics plugin (if installed) allows to connect the WordPress website with Google Analytics to show visitors activity on the website and other statistics.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Google Tag Manager for WordPress (gtm4wp.com)
This Google Tag Manager plugin (if installed) automatically places GTM container code snippets onto the website and complements the GTM setup by pushing page and user meta data into the data layer.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Contact Developer for Usage Details.
Gravity Forms (Rocketgenius, Inc.)
Gravity Forms brings a wide variety of form field inputs to your fingertips (if installed), and allows to select fields, configure options, and easily embed forms on WordPress site using the built in tools.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Gravity Forms PayPal Standard Add-On (Rocketgenius, Inc.)
Gravity Forms PayPal Add-On (if installed) integrates Gravity Forms with PayPal Payments Standard, enabling end users to purchase goods and services through Gravity Forms.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Hupso Share Buttons for Twitter, Facebook & Google+ (kasal)
Hupso Share Buttons for Twitter, Facebook & Google+ plugin (if installed) adds simple social share buttons to posts or pages and enables visitors to share content on the most popular social networks.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy | Contact Developer for Usage Details.
Image Widget (Modern Tribe, Inc.)
Image Widget plugin (if installed) uses the native WordPress media manager to add image widgets to the website.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Scroll Triggered Box (DreamGrow)
Scroll Triggered Box plugin (if installed) helps to increase the conversion rate for Newsletter sign-ups, Like button clicks or social bookmarking when visitors engage with the website.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Scroll Triggered Boxes (ibericode BV)
Scroll Triggered Boxes lightweight plugin (if installed) helps adding flexible call-to-actions boxes to the website, and can contain whatever content you like: shortcodes, links, custom HTML, etc.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: Netherlands – Privacy Policy.
Social Media Flying Icons | Floating SM Icon (Acurax Technologies)
Social Media Flying Icons | Floating Social Media Icon plugin (if installed) is a complete solution that enables interactive social media icons on the website which links to the social media profiles.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States / India – Terms & Conditions.
Social Media Widget (Tatwa Technologies, Ltd.)
Social Media Widget plugin (if installed) takes a simple, extendable approach for displaying the social media profiles on WordPress websites.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: India – Contact Developer for Usage Details.
Social Media Widget (Acurax Technologies)
This Social Media Widget plugin (if installed) links website’s social media icons to Twitter, Facebook, Pinterest, YouTube, RSS Feed, LinkedIn, Google+ social media profiles.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States / India – Terms & Conditions.
Ultimate Social Media PLUS (Social Share Pro)
Ultimate Social Media PLUS plugin (if installed) allows to add social media and share icons to blog, Facebook, Twitter, Email, RSS, Pinterest, Instagram, Google+, LinkedIn, etc.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Contact Developer for Usage Details.
UpdraftPlus – Backup/Restore (Simba Hosting Ltd.)
UpdraftPlus is a popular plugin for WordPress that allows to backup, restore, or even migrate the whole website with just a few clicks. This plugin (if installed) gives access to features such as backup scheduling and external cloud storage, and allows for expansion of the base plugin features using add-ons.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United Kingdom – Data Protection and Privacy Centre.
Wordfence Security (Defiant, Inc.)
Wordfence is the most downloaded security plugin for WordPress websites, which provides the robust protection against cyber criminals and hackers (if installed).
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
WordPress Mobile Pack PRO (Appticles.com)
WordPress Mobile Pack PRO plugin (if installed) comes with more fully customizable app themes, social features, monetization options, and ongoing features and security updates.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Cookie Policy.
WPtouch Mobile & WPtouch Pro (WPtouch Pro)
WPtouch Mobile and WPtouch Pro plugins (if installed) automatically add a simple and elegant mobile theme to the WordPress website to accommodate its mobile visitors.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Yoast SEO (Yoast BV, a Dutch LLC.)
Yoast SEO is a widely popular WordPress plugin that (if installed) can help make the website search engine-friendly.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: Netherlands – Privacy Policy.
User Database Management
This type of service allows the Owner to build user profiles by starting from an email address, a personal name, or other information that the User provides to this Website, as well as to track User activities through analytics features. This Personal Data may also be matched with publicly available information about the User (such as social networks’ profiles) and used to build private profiles that the Owner can display and use for improving this Website. Some of these services may also enable the sending of timed messages to the User, such as emails based on specific actions performed on this Website.
Displaying Content from External Platforms
This type of service allows you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of this Website and interact with them. This type of service might still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it. The Owner encourages the Users to familiarize themselves with Privacy Policies of the most commonly used external platforms regardless if they are actually used on this Website or not.
Instagram (Facebook, Inc.)
Instagram is a photo and video-sharing social networking service owned by Facebook, Inc. that allows this Website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages (if installed).
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Vimeo Video (Vimeo, LLC)
Vimeo is a video content visualization service provided by Vimeo, LLC that allows this Website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages (if installed).
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
YouTube Video Widget (Google Inc.)
YouTube is a video content visualization service provided by Google Inc. that allows this Website to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.
Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data.
Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.
Interaction with Live Chat Platforms
This type of service allows Users to interact with third-party live chat platforms directly from the pages of this Website, for contacting and being contacted by this Website support service. If one of these services is installed, it may collect browsing and Usage Data in the pages where it is installed, even if the Users do not actively use the service. Moreover, live chat conversations may be logged.
Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting
This type of service (if installed) allows this Website and its partners to inform, optimize and serve advertising based on past use of this Website by the User. This activity is performed by tracking Usage Data and by using Cookies, information that is transferred to the partners that manage the remarketing and behavioral targeting activity. In addition to any opt out offered by any of the services below, the User may opt out of a third-party service’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.
The Rights of Users
Users may exercise certain rights regarding their Data processed by the Owner. In particular, Users have the right to do the following:
Withdraw their consent at any time. Users have the right to withdraw consent where they have previously given their consent to the processing of their Personal Data.
Object to processing of their Data. Users have the right to object to the processing of their Data if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent. Further details are provided in the dedicated section below.
Access their Data. Users have the right to learn if Data is being processed by the Owner, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the Data undergoing processing.
>Verify and seek rectification. Users have the right to verify the accuracy of their Data and ask for it to be updated or corrected.
Restrict the processing of their Data. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of their Data. In this case, the Owner will not process their Data for any purpose other than storing it.
Have their Personal Data deleted or otherwise removed. Users have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of their Data from the Owner.
Receive their Data and have it transferred to another controller. Users have the right to receive their Data in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance. This provision is applicable provided that the Data is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on the User’s consent, on a contract which the User is part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof.
Lodge a complaint. Users have the right to bring a claim before their competent data protection authority.
Details About the Right to Object to Processing
Where Personal Data is processed for a public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in the Owner or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Owner, Users may object to such processing by providing a ground related to their particular situation to justify the objection.
Users must know that, however, should their Personal Data be processed for direct marketing purposes, they can object to that processing at any time without providing any justification. To learn, whether the Owner is processing Personal Data for direct marketing purposes, Users may refer to the relevant sections of this document.
How to Exercise These Rights
Any requests to exercise User rights can be directed to the Owner through the contact details provided in this document. These requests can be exercised free of charge and will be addressed by the Owner as early as possible and always within one month.
Additional Information About Data Collection and Processing
Legal Action
The User’s Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Website or the related Services. The User declares to be aware that the Owner may be required to reveal personal data upon request of public authorities.
Additional Information About User’s Personal Data
In addition to the information contained in this privacy policy, this Website may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular Services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request.
System Logs and Maintenance
For operation and maintenance purposes, this Website and any third-party services may collect files that record interaction with this Website (system logs) and use other Personal Data (such as the IP Address) for this purpose.
Information Not Contained in This Policy
More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Owner at any time. Please see the contact information at the beginning of this document.
How “Do Not Track” Requests are Handled
“Do Not Track” (DNT) is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable DNT by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser. The Owner honors DNT signals and this website does not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a DNT browser mechanism is in place.
California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA)
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. According to CalOPPA, the Owner agrees that users can visit this site anonymously. Once this privacy policy is created, the Owner will add a link to it on the footer of the home page. Learn More.
Children Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.
This website, its offerings and the professional services are not intended or catered to anyone under the age of 13. This website does not specifically market to children under 13 and do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13.
If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your children have provided the personal data through this website, please contact us. If the Owner becomes aware that the personal data from children was collected without verification of parental consent, the Owner will take steps to remove that information from his servers. Learn More.
International Users
The Users accessing this website from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from United States laws, should be advised that through their continued use, which is governed by the law of the United States and this Privacy Policy, they will be transferring their personal information into the United States and consent to that transfer.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
The Owner reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page and possibly within this Website and/or – as far as technically and legally feasible – sending a notice to Users via any contact information available to the Owner. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. Should the changes affect processing activities performed on the basis of the User’s consent, the Owner shall collect new consent from the User, where required.
Contact Us
If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, contact the Owner using the information below:
Cancer Patients Alliance
312 Fountain Avenue
Pacific Grove, CA 93950, USA
info@pancreatica.org
Last Updated: May 24, 2018
© 2020 Pancreatica. All rights reserved | Privacy Policy312 Fountain Avenue, Pacific Grove, California 93950   |   Phone: (831) 658-0600   |   Fax: (831) 658-0518  |  participate@tofightcancer.com
Facebook-f
Twitter
Envelope
Youtube
HELP US SHINE A LIGHT ON PANCREATIC CANCER THIS GIVING SEASON !
DONATE TODAY
Thank you for your kind consideration!
